question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right up&quot; upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Team Fortress 2&quot;, the &quot;Bill&#039;s Hat&quot; is a reference to the game &quot;Dota 2&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Fiat Multipla is a drivable car in &quot;Forza Horizon 3&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Return to Castle Wolfenstein&quot; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William &quot;B.J.&quot; Blazkowicz.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
